♪Come closer♪
اقترب ♪
♪Be more intimate♪
♪ كن أكثر حميمية
♪Tell me if I am tempted♪
♪ قل لي إن كنت أغوى
♪The moment you and I looked at each other♪
♪ في اللحظة التي نظرت فيها أنا وأنت إلى بعضنا البعض
♪We were both tempted♪
كلانا أغوى
♪Remember how shy you were♪
♪ تذكر كم كنت خجولًا ♪
♪That day♪
♪ ذلك اليوم ♪
♪Sweet memories♪
♪ ذكريات حلوة ♪
♪Please be more♪
♪ من فضلك كن اكثر
♪How lucky I am to have you♪
♪ كم أنا محظوظ لوجودك ♪
♪So sweet♪
♪ حلوة جدا ♪
=My Naughty Assistant=
= مساعدي المشاغب =
=Episode 2=
= الحلقة 2 =
(Oh.)
(أوه.)
(My head hurts.)
(رأسي يؤلمني.)
(Where am I?)
(أين أنا؟)
(Did I...?)
(هل أنا ...؟)
(Did I get into the world of the drama?)
(هل دخلت عالم الدراما؟)
(Where am I?)
(أين أنا؟)
(Who is he?)
(من هذا؟)
(Did we...?)
(هل فعلنا...؟)
(Did we have sex last night?)
(هل مارسنا الجنس الليلة الماضية؟)
(I'll just leave.)
(سأغادر فقط.)
You're awake?
انت مستيقظ؟
(Isn't he the unapproachable star, Xing Enchen?)
(أليس هو النجم الذي لا يقترب ، Xing Enchen؟)
I...
أنا...
Come and have breakfast.
تعال وتناول الإفطار.
(Calm down!)
(هدء من روعك!)
(Let me...)
(دعني...)
(Let me figure it out.)
(اسمحوا لي أن الرقم بها.)
Just to be clear,
فقط لأكون واضحا،
regardless of whoever you are,
بغض النظر عمن تكون ،
whatever happened to us yesterday,
مهما حدث لنا بالأمس ،
I...
أنا...
I don't remember anything.
لا أتذكر أي شيء.
You don't remember anything?
ألا تتذكر أي شيء؟
Remember what?
تذكر ماذا؟
I don't remember.
أنا لا أتذكر.
Lovely decor.
ديكور جميل.
Very tasteful.
لذيذ جدا.
(Successful man and great house.)
(رجل ناجح وبيت عظيم.)
(Seems that she really got silly after the bump.)
(يبدو أنها أصبحت سخيفة حقًا بعد الصدمة).
(What should I do?)
(ماذا علي أن أفعل؟)
(So handsome.)
(وسيم جدا.)
(God sends me a handsome man.)
(أرسلني الله رجلاً وسيمًا).
(No, no.)
(مهووس.)
(It's not the time to think about that.)
(هذا ليس الوقت المناسب للتفكير في ذلك).
Why is my ID card here?
لماذا بطاقة هويتي هنا؟
What a beautiful day!
يا له من يوم جميل!
Where am I, exactly?
أين أنا بالضبط؟
You have
عندك
a nice tie.
ربطة عنق جميلة.
Shared with male models.
مشترك مع عارضين ذكور.
I will leave after breakfast.
سوف أغادر بعد الإفطار.
The next one is coming in half an hour.
القادم سيأتي بعد نصف ساعة.
Wait.
انتظر.
Say it clearly.
قلها بوضوح.
This is my assistant.
هذا هو مساعدي.
Not a shared one.
ليست مشتركة.
If there's anything, go to her.
إذا كان هناك أي شيء ، اذهب إليها.
Wait.
انتظر.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Last night, we...
الليلة الماضية ، نحن ...
You snored last night.
لقد شخرت الليلة الماضية.
I'll keep it a secret.
سأبقي الأمر سرا.
(Nonsense.)
(كلام فارغ.)
(I don't snore.)
(أنا لا أشخر.)
(What actually happened last night?)
(ما الذي حدث بالفعل الليلة الماضية؟)
Who's it?
من هو؟
Duoduo.
ديودو.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
I brought you breakfast.
أحضرت لك الإفطار.
♪How many times in my life♪
♪ كم مرة في حياتي ♪
♪I am destined♪
أنا مقدر ♪
♪To meet you and fall in love with you♪
♪ لمقابلتك والوقوع في حبك
♪In my finest age♪
♪ في خيرة عمري ♪
♪It's a pity♪
♪ إنه لأمر مؤسف
♪That we are not together in this life♪
بأننا لسنا معًا في هذه الحياة
♪But still, thank you♪
♪ لكن مع ذلك ، شكرًا لك ♪
♪For letting me♪
♪ لسماحك لي ♪
♪Walk into your world♪
♪ امش في عالمك ♪